GUNNAR HARRISON (he/him) is a multidisciplinary graphic designer based in Salt Lake City, Utah. His practice incorporates Identity Design, Motion Graphics, Image Making, UI/UX Design, Type Design, and Front-End Development. He has worked with a range of clients including: Nike, A24 Films, Google, Apple, Nécessaire, Otis College of Art and Design, ArtBook, Actual Source Books, and others.

EXPERIENCE

Apple (Remote Contract)

Salt Lake City, UT

Senior Graphic Designer Apr 2021 – Present

Actual Source

Provo, UT

Senior Graphic Designer Feb 2020 – Apr 2021 Graphic Designer Apr 2018 – Jan 2020 Graphic Design Intern Jan 2018 – Apr 2018

214 Co.

New York, NY

Graphic Design Intern May 2017 – Aug 2017

Wallaroo Media

Provo, UT

Graphic Designer May 2015 – May 2017

EDUCATION

Brigham Young University

BFA Graphic Design Jun 2014 – Apr 2018

SKILLS

Adobe CC (Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, AfterEffects, Media Encoder, XD), Figma, Cinema 4D, Glyphs, Git, HTML, CSS, jQuery

AWARDS

ADC Young One Silver Cube	2018
Graphis New Talent Gold	2018
Graphis New Talent Silver	2018
Bryan Peterson Scholarship	2017
McCray Magleby Scholarship	2017
Talent Award Scholarship	2016

FEATURES

Mouthwash	Web, 2020
The Brand Identity	Web, 2020
New Aesthetic 1	Print, 2019
BYU CFAC	Web, 2018
Klikkenthéke	Web, 2018
Extra Point	Print , 2018
DesignArts Utah	Exhibition, 2017

WEBSITE gunnaris.me

EMAIL hello@gunnaris.me